https://www.thewritingdesk.co.uk/content/privacy-policy.html

> Privacy PolicyOur Privacy PolicyIntroductionThe Writing Desk is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers while providing the highest possible quality of service. We only use the information we collect about you lawfully and we are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998. Our Data Protection Registration Number is Z3624446. This Privacy Notice explains in detail the types of personal data we may collect about you when you interact with us. It also explains how we’ll store and handle that data, and keep it safe. It’s likely that we will need to update this Privacy Notice from time to time. We will notify you of any significant changes, but you’re welcome to come back and check it whenever you wish. All of the information that you supply when placing an order or when you e-mail us is stored securely on a server within the UK and we fully comply and observe the conditions of UK Data Protection as laid down in the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR) and Consumer legislation from time to time in place.There are a number of different reasons for which a company may collect your personal data. With your consent we can collect your data for example when you tick a box to receive a newsletter. We will need your personal information for certain contractual obligations for example if you order an item for delivery we will need to collect your address so that we can pass them on to our delivery partner. We may also need to collect your personal information for legal compliance for example to pass on information relating to a fraud or a crime. We will also collect and use your personal data for legitimate interests which we may reasonably be expected to have as part of running a business. For example we may use your purchase history to send you personalised offers, to keep up with demands, or to develop new products and services.The type of information we collect from you includes:Your NameE-mail addressBilling addressDelivery addressTelephone numberProduct selectionsPassword (this is stored in encrypted form)Credit/debit card details when placing an order by phone (your debit/credit card details are never held on any of our computers and they are destroyed as soon as your order has been processed)Other payment informationThe information that we hold as the Data Controller is collected in the following situations:When you use our website and use your accountWhen you make an online purchaseWhen you engage with us on social mediaWhen you contact us by any meansWhen you enter competitionsWhen you comment on or review a productWhen you leave a shop testimonialIt is stored only for the normal handling and despatch of ordered goods as well as in our legitimate interests in the operation of our retail company. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You may check the information that we hold about you by e-mailing us. If there are any inaccuracies we will correct it or delete it promptly.Website CookiesOur website software requires the use of "cookies" that are an essential part of the ordering process (the shopping basket cannot function without cookies). Cookies are small text files held on your computer which only our website can read. No personal information is ever held in a cookie.In addition, our website sets two Google Analytics cookies to help us monitor site visits and customer behaviour. All data gathered by this method is totally anonymous.You'll be pleased to know that we don't use any tracking cookies or any third party cookies that target you with advertising on other platforms. They're really annoying!By using our website you agree to our cookies being stored on your computer.In summary we use your information only for the following purposes:Processing your orders and enquiriesFor statistical or survey purposes to improve this Website and its services to youTo administer the WebsiteIn the detection and prevention of fraud or other crimesTo assist with any of your customer enquiriesWe may occasionally use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, services or any new or special offers we think you would find valuable.When you create an account while ordering online you will be given the option to consent to receive a newsletter (usually 1 or 2 e-mails per month) from The Writing Desk. You can also sign-up to our newsletter list by entering your e-mail address in the sign-up box at the bottom of each page (you will receive an automated e-mail asking you to confirm your request). You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by following the link at the bottom of the newsletter e-mail, by updating your personal information in your account or else by replying with the word "remove" as the e-mail subject.We will never sell or disclose your personal information to a third party or use your information for purposes other than described in this policy. We may give your personal information to our trusted service partners for the necessary purposes of processing payment and delivery of your order. We will ensure our trusted partners keep your personal information safe and uphold the required Data Protection Policies.We are a totally independent business so we do not have any sister or partner companies.You have the following rights:To be informed that we hold data about youTo access the data we hold about youTo have your data rectifiedTo have your data erased*To restrict the processing of your dataTo data portabilityTo objectIf you have any concerns about the processing and use of your personal information please contact us at orders@thewritingdesk.co.uk To contact the regulatory body please contact the Information Commissioner’s Office https:/ico.org/concerns/* for accounting reasons we cannot completely delete customer information as we are required to retain order history. However, we can reduce personal information to name only by removing addresses upon request.The Writing Desk Ltd. is registered in England. Company Number 8406894. Registered company address 53 Horsecroft Road, Bury St Edmunds, IP33 2DT, UK.
Specials
Kaweco Al Sport Gold Special Edition
£ 75.60
-10%
£ 84.00
All specials BlogArticlesBuyer's guidesTutorials & DIYRecent Blog articles
Testimonials ( 4869 )
(5,0/5)
Review By Paul Bragg,
An excellent service from Martin and the Writing Desk. All my queries were answered fully. My &quo ... 20-11-2020 Review By Christopher,
My TWSBI mechanical pencil arrived so quickly I didn't realise what was in the parcel. Ordered at 11 ... 20-11-2020 Review By Victoria Stevenson,
I received my parcel the day after I ordered it. And the Writing Desk answered my query almost immed ... 19-11-2020 See all Reviews
